（古市）＜おっす　オレ　古市！→
Wazzap! Furuichi here!
魔界です！
オレ　今　ここ魔界です　マジ！→
This is the Demon World! We're here,
in the Demon World! Seriously!
え？なんでこんなに
テンション高いかって？→
Oh? Why am I so high strung?
いや～　高くないですよ　別に。
フツーです！→
I'm not that high strung, really!
Totally normal!
いたってフツーに
前回の　あらすじ！＞
A perfectly normal recap
of what happened last time!
（古市）((アランドロンの娘が
かわいい…))
Alaindelon's daughter is... cute!
((かわいいぞ～！))
She's damn cute!
We're Back, Demon World!
（ラミア）きもいんですけど…。
何？今の絵。
You're creeping me out.
What was that picture just now?
あの　そのマジ引き
やめてもらえる？
Um, would you stop shying
away from me like that?
まだ　冷ややかな方が…。
I'd even prefer cold stares to that.
だって　きもいんだもん。
（男鹿）ああ　きもいな。
Cause you're creepy.
Yeah, creepy.
（ベル坊）アイアイ。
おい！ベル坊まで。
Hey!
Wait!
ひっ！
いやいや　だって見ろよ　これ！
Wait, wait! Look at this!
あの　おっさんの娘とは
思えねえほど美人だぞ！→
That old guy's daughter is more
beautiful than you'd think!
おい！見ろよ　ベル坊も！
わかったから　どうどう。
Look at her! You too, Baby Beel!
I get it, so down boy!
（ピピピ…）
[TEL]（通信器：ヒルダ）おい　お前ら→
You don't get it! This amazing beauty...
Stop it, people. Drop the subject.
もうその辺にしておけ。
事態は一刻を争うのだ。→
You're in a battle against time.
下らん話をしている暇はないぞ。
ヒルダさん！
You do not have time to
engage in pointless chatter.
Hilda-san!
[TEL]それに　古市がきもいのは
最初からだ。
And besides...
Furuichi has always been creepy.
ああ…そう…。
Is that so?
（ガレ）
アジトまで連れてけ？
おいおい　なめてんじゃねえぞ→
Lead you to our base?
Come on now! Don't underestimate us.
オレたちが　仲間を売るとでも
思ってんのか？
You really think we'd sell out our buddies?
（エッダ）ヘッ！そういうこった。→
That's how it is.
魔獣に喰われて死ね　カスが。
Get eaten by a Demon Beast and die, scum!
王族の権力なんて関係ねえ。→
Royal power doesn't matter here.
どんな拷問されようと
口を割るわけねえだろ　ボケ！
Now matter what torture you try,
our mouths'll stay shut, pinheads!
ヘッ！そういうこった。
魔獣に喰われて死ね　カスが。
That's how it is.
Get eaten by a Demon Beast and die, scum!
うん？
あそこか。
Over there?
間違いねえんだろうな？
This is the place, right?
（エッダ）は　はい！そりゃあもう！
R-Right! So can you...
（ガレ）あの一番大きな建物に
幽閉されてるはずですから。
She should be kept locked
up in that highest tower!
何されたのかしら。
What did he do to them?
ああ　オレ　こういうの
見たことある。
Oh, I've seen this happen before...
街？ああ　それなら聞いたことがある。
A city? Yes, I've heard of it.
ヴラドの盗賊街。
古代の遺跡に住み着き→
Vlad's Den of Thieves.
They live in the remains of an ancient city,
魔境の魔獣を乱獲している連中だ。
and poach the Demon Beasts in the Haunt.
[TEL]（古市）ヒルダさん！
そんなことより→
Hilda-san! Anyway, can I ask you something?
ひとつ聞いていいっすか！？
なんだ？
What is it?
[TEL]（古市）
あ　あの　おっさんの
娘さんのお名前なんですが！
U-Um... What's the name
of the big guy's daughter?
名前？ああ　そうだったな
アランドロンの娘の名は…。
Her name? Oh, yes...
Alaindelon's daughter's name is...
[TEL]（古市）娘の名は…！？
Her name is...
Ang...
[TEL]アンジ…。
（ピィー　ガー…プツッ！）
えっ！？切れた！何で！？
It cut off! Why?
ヒルダさん　ちょっと！
アンジ　なんですか！？→
Hilda-san, wait! Ang-what?
そこ　重要なんですけど～！
うわっ！ここ圏外！？
That's really important!
No Service?!
アンじ～さんじゃね？
ダ。
She'd be Angie-san, right?
っていうか！
これから　どうするんですか～！
And anyway, what'll we do now?!
（おかしら）くっくっく…。→
くく　八十一。
9(ku) times 9(ku) equals 81.
*silence*
（パン！パン！）
（手下）おい！
（ザンガ）笑え！
Come on!
Laugh!
（手下たち）わははは！
≪あざ～っす！
おかしら　もう最高っす！≫
You're the best, Boss!
ふふん　どうだ？
少しは　協力する気になったか？→
How about that? Are you reconsidering
helping us now, Angelica-kun?
アンジェリカ君。
（アンジェリカ）
何度言われても同じです。→
My answer is the same,
no matter what you say.
泥棒の片棒を担ぐ気はありません。
捉えた魔獣を放しなさい。
I have no intention of aiding thieves.
Release the Demon Beasts you have captured!
ふん！あんなもの
二束三文にしかならん。
Eh, those? They ain't worth much anyway.
お前がひとこと
協力すると言えば　いつでも。
If you say that you'll help
us, whenever you like...
（手下たち）ははは…！
ひぃ～ひひひ！
うるせえ～っ！
（ザンガ）やめろ～！
Shut up!
Stop!
いいかね？アンジェリカ君。→
Listen well, Angelica-kun.
君たち　次元転送悪魔というのはね
わたしら　盗賊の夢だ。→
You people are dimensional
transfer demons, yes?
A thief's dream...
どこへでも忍び込み
人知れず去っていく。→
Sneak in anywhere and leave
before anyone notices.
どんな難攻不落の宝物庫も
空家同然。まさに神出鬼没。
No matter how impregnable the treasure
room, cracking it open would be a cinch!
A true phantom thief.
そうですね。
この手錠さえなければ→
That's right!
If it weren't for these cuffs,
I would disappear this instant!
今すぐ消えてさしあげます。
フフン。
おかしら！
ガレとエッダから通達です！
Boss!
Gallé and Edda sent a message!
王族の者だと！？
Royalty?
Right!
はい！
ここの場所が割れたか。
ふん！まあいい。→
Our location here is blown?
Fine, no matter.
何をしている　警備を固めろ！
（手下）へい！
What do you think you're
doing? Stiffen the guard!
Yes, sir!
はぁ…。→
父さん　今日帰るって言ってたけど
心配してるかな。
Dad said he'd come home today...
I wonder if he's worried...
最悪の誕生日
どうせ　忘れてるんだろうけど。
This is the worst birthday ever...
I'm sure he's forgotten though.
（古市）そんなことはない！→
That's not true!
ドレスを買ってあげるって
言ってましたよ。
He said that he bought you a dress.
あっ！
あなたは？
You're...
ちょっと待ってくださいね。
今　そちらに行きます。
Wait for a moment. I'll head there now.
（アンジェリカ）父のお知り合いの
方ですか？
（古市）ええ　まあ→
Are you a friend of my father's?
Yes! Well, I'm a human though.
人間ですけどね。
（アンジェリカ）人間！？
Human?!
ちょっと…
なんで　私が　こんなこと…。
Hey! Why do I have to do this?
古市様！？
もしかしてあなた　古市様じゃ！
Furuichi-sama? Could you be Furuichi-sama?
《古市…様！？》
Furuichi...-sama?
父から　いつも
お話をうかがっております。
My father always speaks of you!
ええ。あなたを助けに来ました。
古市です！
（アンジェリカ）やっぱり！
Yes. I have come to rescue you.
I am Furuichi.
I knew it!
逃げてください！
え？
Please, escape!
魔獣です！魔獣が来るんです！
ものすごく大きな…。
A Demon Beast... A Demon Beast is coming!
A really, really big one!
魔獣？
Demon Beast?
（地響き）
ダワワ…！キー！
（鳥の鳴き声）
アアッ！
（アンジェリカ）ここの人たちは
魔境を荒しすぎました。→
The people here have done too
much damage to the Haunt.
ヴラドの主が怒ってる
私には　声が聞こえるんです。
Vlad's Guardian is angry.
I can hear its voice.
なんだ　あれは！？
What the heck is that?
（ヴラドの主）ゴオオオ…！
キャー！
う…うう…。
う～んぐ！
フン！フンン～…ぐっ。
あの～…助けてください。
はあ？
ええ～？
Um... Please help.
（ヴラドの主）ゴオオオ…！
ああ…。
ヴラドの主？
Vlad's Guardian?
はい。
Right.
グオオオ…！
ゴオオオ…！
（アンジェリカ）身の丈が
山よりも大きな魔獣です。
A Demon Beast bigger than even the mountains!
（街の人たち）アアア…！
（アンジェリカ）ここの連中は→
The people here have killed
too many Demon Beasts...
魔獣を殺しすぎました。
主は怒っています。
The Guardian is angry!
グオオオーッ！！
キャー！
≪うわあ～！≫
じょ　冗談じゃないぞ
あんな化け物。
You've got to be kidding me! That monster!
あっ！おかしら！→
Boss!
ちょっ…
どこ行くんです　おかしら！
Where are you going, Boss?
I'm taking Angelica with
me and getting out of here!
決まってるだろう！
アンジェリカを連れて→
逃げるんだ！
あの娘だけは手放せん！
She's the only one I won't
let out of my grasp!
ハッ！
Please escape, Furuichi-sama!
逃げてください　古市様！
おかしらが帰ってきます！
Their boss is coming back!
Escape? You're saying to
run and leave you behind?
逃げる？あなたを置いて
どこへ逃げるというのです？
というか　これ
もう逃げられませんから。
But you see... I can no
longer escape from here.
You think that's cool? Furuichi, you idiot!
かっこよくねぇんだよ！
バカ古市！
Your damn head's just stuck, you jerk!
ただ　はさまって
抜けねえだけだろうが！
If we don't get out of here
we'll be stomped flat!
逃げないと
ペシャンコにされるわよ！
アハ！大丈夫　大丈夫。
It's okay. It's okay!
グオオオ…！
It's not "okay" in the slightest!
全然　大丈夫じゃねえんだよ！
ボケェ！
You idiot!
ハッ！
頭が抜けないのですね？
You can't get your head out?
Wait just a moment!
ちょっとお待ちを！
え？
あ　あの…何を。
いきます！
Um, what are you...
Here I go!
Wai...
ちょっ…ゴッ！
（アンジェリカ）フン！フン！フン！
（ゴン！ゴン！ゴン！）
ウウ…あ…あ…。
はぁ　はぁ　抜けませんわね。
You are quite stuck.
What shall we do?
どうしよう。このままじゃ
あなたがひどい目に。
At this rate, you will suffer greatly!
《この人…天然だ…殺される》
She's oblivious!
I'm gonna get killed...
アンジェリカ！→
Angelica!
What are you doing? We're
getting out of here!
なにをしている　逃げるぞ！
ここはもうダメだ！→
This place has gone to hell!
A crazy monster has shown up!
とんでもねえ化け物が
こっちに来てやがる！
（カギを開ける音）
うん？
ふん　例の王族の
契約者とかいう人間か。→
So you're that human with a
contract with the royal family...
Guess you came to rescue her,
but it's too bad for you.
娘を助けに来たんだろうが
残念だったな。→
Circle around and get him!
回り込んでやっちまえ！
油断するな！仲間もいるはずだ！
Don't let your guard down! He
should have friends with him!
Yes, sir!
（手下たち）はっ！
くせ者だ！出会え～！
You bastards!
Hey, hey, hey... This is what they call
one of those "do-or-die" moments, right?
おいおいおい　こりゃあ
大ピンチってやつじゃねぇか？
Why do you seem so happy about it?
なんでそんなに嬉しそうなのよ。
I'm all excited!
わくわくしてきたぞ！
（ラミア）しないわよ！→
Well, I'm not!
Are you some kind of warrior race?!
どこの戦闘民族よ！
It'll be fun.
楽しめよ。男っていうのはな
ピンチの時ほど笑うもんだ。
A man, see... The harder the
situation, the more a man laughs!
And when he does, power
comes flowing up naturally.
そうすりゃ　自然と
力もわいてくる。
Well I'm a woman!
私は女よ！
Isn't that right, Baby Beel?
なあ　ベル坊。
あ？ベル坊？
Baby Beel?
べるぜ様？
Beelze-sama?
グルルル…。
What're you standin' there for?
何を突っ立っておる！
Master Zanga!
ザンガ様！
ええい　のけ！わしがやる！→
Stand aside!
I'll do it!
Royal stooges, you now
face the fearsome Zanga!
王族のものとやらっ
わしは目付役のザンガと申す！
Fight me fair and...
いざ尋常に～しょう…ぶっ！
はっ　なっ　なんと～！
W-What?!
Baby Beel... What exactly are you...
ベル坊君　これはいったい…。
Power is overflowing from him!
力が　わき出して
らっしゃるのでは…。
アーーーッ！！
ゴァアアアッ！！
ダーーーッ！！
ガァアアアアッ！！
ダーブーー！！
おぉ…あぁ…！！
ゴァアアアアッ！！
アーーーッ！！
なんだ？
What's that?
アーーーッ！！
（古市）ぎゃあああっ！
（ザンガと手下）ああああっ！
ダーーーッ！！
B-Baby Beel?!
ベ…ベル坊！？
Baby got big!
でっかくなっちゃった～っ！
I'm free! Lamia, what's wrong?! Where's Oga?
とれたっ！
ラミア　なんだあれ？
男鹿は！？うっ。
ゴゴゴゴ…。
ダーブー。
ニュク　ウッ。
Oga's on him!
乗ってる～っ！！
There are two monsters! What's going on?!
化け物が２匹！！
なんなんだ　これは！？
ヨッ…ウッ…。
あ？
ダーブー！
ゴゴゴゴ…。
ブルルル…。
Go, Giant Beelbo!
ゆけっ！ベツ人二十八号！！
ダーーブッ！
ダーッ！
ゴァアアアッ！！
《なんだ…これ》
What the heck.
ウゥー。
Here it comes!
ひっ。
くるぞ～！
逃げろ～！！
Run for it!
アアアアア…。
Do a Giant Beelbo Kick!
ベツ人キックだ！
ダッ！
ベツ人～っ　キーック！
Giant Beelbo Kick!
アーチャー！！
ゴォオオオ！
Gimme a...
おいおい。
まさか…。
You're kidding me.
ぎゃああああっ！
わはははっ…見たか巨大怪獣！
おっとっと　こ　こえ～！
That hurt, you giant monster?
Scary...
あ～。
む　むちゃくちゃだ…。
He's nuts.
ゴォオオオオ…。
ブルルルル…。
はあ　はあ…。フー　やべえ。
That was close.
Things have really gotten fun!
なんか楽しくなってきちゃったぞ。
Ready, Baby Beel? Next up, do
a Giant Beelbo Clothesline!
よ～し　ベル坊！
お次は　ベツ人ボンバーだ！！
ベル坊？
Baby Beel?
ンダッ！
うおおおおっ！こえ～～っ！！
Giant Beelbo... Clothesline!
ベツ人～っ　ボンバーッ！！
Giant Beelbo... Elbow!
ベツ人～っ　エルボーッ！！
ははははっ。よ～し　とどめだ！
Now the final blow!
あああ…。
あっ…。
Giant Beelbo...
ベツ人～っ　逆海老固め！！
Boston Crab!
（ヴラドの主）ゴァアアアアッ！！
（街の人たち）おぉ…。
ダーーーッ！！
（街の人）
うおおおお　やりやがった！
He did it!
That big baby-looking thing beat the monster!
（街の人）あの赤ん坊っぽいの
怪物を倒したぞ！
Wow! Was it protecting us?
（街の人）すげえ！オレたちを
守ってくれたのか！？
Amazing!
すげ～ぞっ！
街は　ほぼ全壊だけど…。
I mean, most of the city
is destroyed, but hey...
ダーブー！
アーーッ！！
アーーーッ！！
What is it trying to do?!
（街の人たち）何がしたいんだ～！
うっ　うぬう…なんてことだ。わしの街が。
I can't believe this...
My city...
Hold it. That's as far as you go.
（古市）おっと　そこまでだ。
Would you do me a favor and let
her go... my fine-bearded friend?
その子を放してもらおうか。
ヒゲメーン。
Or maybe you'd like to dance with me?
それともオレと　踊るかい？
Furuichi-sama!
古市様！
ううっ　小僧。
You little brat!
Idiot! You're actually a complete idiot!
バカだ…本物のバカだ。
あんた　弱いんでしょう？
I know you're totally weak.
刃物か…やめときな　そんなの。
A dagger, is it?
Don't even try it.
《う～わっ
ナイフ出てきちゃったよ！！》
He pulled a knife!
怪我するぜ。
《オレが》
Someone's gonna get hurt...
...like me!
Huh? What do you mean?
何だと？どういう意味だ！？
（古市）
《くそう　弱そうだと思ったに…》
Crap! I thought he looked weak!
What? Well, you know... that.
なぜって…それは　あれだ。
どれだ！？
What?
You see, there's this death move passed
down through the generations...
え～つまり　一子相伝の
暗殺拳がだな長男と三男の間で…。
Between the eldest and third to eldest son...
What are you talking about?!
なんの話～！？
ダッ！！
はっ！
Um...
え～っと　つまり
こうなるってことさ！！
In other words.
This happens!
フッ。
ムリヤリ決めた～！！
As if you caused that coincidence!
アーーッ！！
アーイー！！
フフフフ…フフフフ…→
I mean, whoa, that was close, Oga!
つ～か　おいっ！！
危ね～だろ　男鹿！！→
I was in the crack between his toes!
今のオレ　指の隙間だったぞ！→
I'm glad I sounded kind of cool, but...
たまたま　うまくいったから
よかったものの→
Are you even listening to me?
聞いてんのか　おいっ！！
お…え？ちょ…。
ブルルルル…。
（３人）うわぁあああ！！
ウッウッ　アーアイアイ！！
うわぁあああ！
あぶ　あぶなっ！
Whoa there!
ひぃいいい　主よりたちが悪い！！
This guy's worse than the Guardian!
Hey now, hey now... What's going on?
おいおいおいっ　なんだ　これ！？
ベルゼ様　暴走？
Beelze-sama's out of control!
男鹿は何してんだよっ！！
What are you doing, Oga?
Yo.
おっす。
て　なぜか前にいたっ！！
And why are you here in front of us?
He threw me off.
振り落とされました。
よく生きてたなっ！！
You're damn lucky you survived!
興奮してるんだわ。
どうにかして止めないと…。
He's overly excited! We
have to calm him somehow!
Sure, but how?
そんなこと言っても　どうやって？
きゃあ！！
ラミア！！
えいっ。
Lamia!
ダーブー！！
とまれっ！！ベル坊！
Stop, Baby Beel!
はっ！
I-It's no use!
って　無理か～！
きゃあああ！！
くっ。
ごはんですよ～～っ！！
It's dinner time!
アーッ！！
戻った…。
He turned back.
犬か。
What is he, a dog?
アーッ！ダブー！ダーダブ！！
What a pain you are...
…ったく　面倒かけやがって。
（古市）＜こうして　オレ達の冒険は
終わりを迎えた。→
And like that, our adventure
headed to its conclusion.
Without their boss, the poachers
left gradually a few at a time.
頭を失った盗賊たちは　三々五々
ちりぢりに消えた。→
And with no one there, the Demon Beasts
imprisoned in the hideout all escaped.
誰もいなくなったアジトに幽閉
されていた魔獣たちも逃がした。→
But most surprising was Angelica-san.
驚いたのは　アンジェリカさん。→
She explained the situation to
that giant, Vlad's Guardian,
あの大きなヴラドの主を説得して
魔境へと帰してしまった。→
who went back to the Haunt...
And so... the time has come to say goodbye.
そして　別れの時がやってきた＞
（ラミア）
ひっく　うぐ　うっ…ベルゼ様ぁ。
Beelze-sama!
Hey, don't cry...
おいおい　泣くなよ。
（ラミア）だって～ひっく。
But!
Man, you're such a little kid.
…ったく　やっぱガキだな。
Are you really so upset we have to leave?
そんなにオレたちと
離れんのがイヤか？
Who said anything about you?
あんたは入ってないわよ！！
うぉっ！くっ…。
I'm sad and depressed about
having to leave Beelze-sama!
私はベルゼ様と離れんのが
悲しいのっ！寂しいのっ！！
Who'd give a lick about you, huh? So rude!
誰が　あんたなんかで
泣くもんですか！失礼なっ！
This again?
また　これかよ…。
Well... You did try to save me back there...
まあ…さっき
助けようとしてくれたことは→
I'll give you my thanks for that.
お礼　言っとくわよ　一応。
あぁ？
I guess.
（ラミア）
と　とにかく　ベルゼ様のこと
しっかり頼むわよっ！！→
Anyway, you'd better take damn
good care of Beelze-sama!
If you let him get sick again,
I'll never forgive you!
また病気になんてさせたら
許さないから！！
Yeah. If that happens again, I'll call you.
あ～。
そん時ゃ　またお前を呼ぶよ。
あっ…。
早く　行きなさいよ。
Hurry up and go.
It doesn't really matter, but transferring
in Angelica-san would be...
《ど～でもいいけど
アンジェリカさんに→
転送してもらうということは
彼女も割れるのだろうか？》
I wonder if she splits, too?
((パカッ))
And then... inside her...
《そして　その中に…
なんかエロイぞ！！》
That's kind of hot...
Well then, shall we go?
では　まいりましょうか！
《はっ　きた～っ！！》
Here I go!
あ　父が…。
（アランドロン）どうも～。
Actually, my father will...
Hello!
Sorry about not saying anything...
He just came a moment ago.
あの…黙っててすみません。
少し前に来てたんですけど→
There wasn't really a time to tell you...
言い出すタイミングがなくて…。
Everyone looks like they are safe and sound.
みなさん　ご無事のようで…
何よりですな。
And if you have your health...
（男鹿・古市・ラミア）アランドロン！！
（アランドロン）はい。
Alaindelon!
Yes?
（男鹿・古市・ラミア）生きてたの！？
ダブダダダ！？
You're still alive?!
はっはっはっ　あれしきのことで
死にませんよ。
I wouldn't die from something like that.
Screw you! Where have you been?
てめえ　ふざけんなよっ！
今までどこに！
傷を癒すために健康ランドへ…。
I went to a health resort to heal my wounds.
Demon World Health Resort
The Destopia Bloodpools
((あ～あぁ～))
ま　そんなことは置いといて。
Leaving that aside.
パカーッ！
うっううう。
うわぁ！！
いやだぁ～～！！→
No!!
ああ～アンジェリカさんに
転送してもらうんだぁ～！
I wanted to be transferred by Angelica-san!
（アランドロン）はっはっはっ
ほ～れ　古市殿～！！
Here we go, Furuichi-dono!
（セミの鳴き声）
I will say this... for now.
とりあえず　こう言っておこう。
はぁはぁはぁ。
Welcome home.
お帰りなさいませ。
ただいま。
We're back.
And, like this, our long, long
summer vacation was over.
（古市）
＜こうして　オレたちの
長い長い夏休みは終わった＞
フーッ。
Summer vacation's over, and it's a new term!
But wait, Ishiyama's still destroyed, right?
Looks like we're transferring
to St. Ishiyama Academy.
So why are you laughing like a creep
and spreading butter on toast?
First day, new transfer;
"I'm late, I'm late"; toast in mouth;
round the corner; bam; fall in love!
On the next Beelzebub:
The New Term Has Started!
Oh, I'm late! I'm late!
Furuichi-dono...
I knew it'd turn out like this...